official-kmspico.com 2019-12-26

# Privacy Policy

## **Welcome to our Privacy Policy**

— **Your privacy is critically important to us** —

It is KMSPico’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website. This Privacy Policy applies to [official-kmspico.com](https://official-kmspico.com/) (hereinafter, “us”, “we”, or “official-kmspico.com”). We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting personally recognizable data you’ll give us through the site.

We have adopted this privacy policy (“ **Privacy Policy** “) to clarify what info is also collected on our site, however, we use this info, and below what circumstances we might disclose the knowledge to third parties. This Privacy Policy applies only to data we collect through the site and doesn’t apply to our collection of data from alternative sources.

This Privacy Policy, along with the Terms and conditions announced on our site, set forth the overall rules and policies governing your use of our website. Looking on your activities when visiting our site, you’ll be needed to comply with extra terms and conditions.

##  **Website Visitors**

Like most website operators, KMSPico collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. KMSPico’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how KMSPico’s visitors use its website.

From time to time, [KMSPico](https://official-kmspico.com/) may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

KMSPico also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on https://official-kmspico.com/ blog posts. KMSPico only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below.

###  **– Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information**

Certain visitors to KMSPico’s websites choose to interact with KMSPico in ways that require KMSPico to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that KMSPico gathers depend on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for a blog at https://official-kmspico.com/ to provide a username and email address.

 **– Security**

The security of your Personal data is very important to us, however, keep in mind that no technique of transmission over the internet, or technique of electronic storage is 100% secure. whereas we attempt to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

##  **– Advertisements**

Ads showing on our website could also be delivered to users by advertising partners, who might set cookies. These cookies enable the ad server to acknowledge your laptop every time they send you an internet advert to compile data about you or others who use your laptop. This data permits ad networks to, among different things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe are of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by KMSPico and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. also, you can read This… [Google Ads policies](https://support.google.com/adspolicy/answer/6008942?hl=en)

##  **– Links To External Sites**

Our Service might contain links to external sites that aren’t operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you’ll be directed to that third party’s website. we strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy and the terms and conditions of each website you visit.  
We have no management over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites, product or services.

 **– Aggregated Statistics**

KMSPico may collect statistics about the behaviour of visitors to its website. KMSPico may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, KMSPico does not disclose your personally-identifying information.

##  **– Cookies**

To enrich and perfect your online experience, KMSPico uses “Cookies”, similar technologies and services provided by others to display personalized content, appropriate advertising and store your preferences on your computer. A cookie is a string of data that a site stores on a visitor’s PC, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the web site every time the visitor returns.

KMSPico uses cookies to help KMSPico identify and track visitors, their usage of https://official-kmspico.com/, and their website access preferences. KMSPico visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using KMSPico’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of KMSPico’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

By continuing to navigate our website without changing your cookie settings, you hereby acknowledge and agree to KMSPico’s use of cookies.

#####  **Privacy Policy Changes**

Although most changes are likely to be minor, **KMSPico** may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in KMSPico’s sole discretion. KMSPico encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continuing use of this website once any modification during this Privacy Policy can represent your acceptance of such change.
